# Jay Massey

jaymassey98@gmail.com ❖ 07450123428 ❖ Worthing ❖ Looking to Relocate to Brighton

I am a Computer Science graduate with over 4 years of customer service experience, from managing a fashion retail sales team, re-merchandising chain stores across multiple regions, and promoting products at marketing exhibitions. My current goal is to pursue a career that will allow me to further improve and diversify my skill set.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **University of Brighton**

11/2019 - 08/2020

**Ambassador** 

Brighton, East Sussex

Chosen to lead university recruitment events based on my previous experience of management.

- Marketed my course through self-led events and exhibitions in order to promote my university.
- Facilitated large tours for prospective students, preparing for potential enquires that may arise.
- Developed how to deescalate queries and complaints whilst remaining professional at all times.

**Peacocks** 

11/2016 - 04/2019

Duty Manager

Hove. East Sussex

Promoted from key holder after demonstrating excellent store knowledge and leadership skills.

- Led a fast-fashion retail chain store for 2+ days a week during my superiors' days off for a year.
- Supervised sales teams of 4 8 people to deliver a consistent high standard of customer service.
- Supported my manager's direction to guide the team into reaching their target figures and KPIs.
- Experienced in handling payroll, cashing up and banking to ensure the store operated efficiently.
- Merchandised multiple stores to aid them in reaching the same high sales I achieved in my store.

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Brighton

09/2017 - 09/2020

BSc (Hons) Computer Science

Brighton, East Sussex

Graduated with a 2.1 (upper-second class) honours degree as a Bachelor of Science.

- Agile Management Managed projects effectively through a variety of agile model practices.
- Product Analysis Developed various system models to meet client's goals and requirements.
- Website Development Constructed websites with HTML and CSS, with experience in Node.js.

A wide variety of professional projects are available at https://jaymassey98.github.io/portfolio.

#### **Previous Education**

09/2011 - 09/2017

Electronics AS (B), Mathematics AS (B), Physics AS (C) – 13 GCSEs, 6 A's, 5 B's, 2 C's, English (2x A).

#### **PERSONAL**

Additional Skills – Socialising; video editing; driving; first aid trained; Microsoft Office, especially Excel.

General Interests - Bouldering; strength training; philosophy; designing; gaming; ice skating; sightseeing.